dondengaeshi detatokoshoubu nerau wa ittou shou
An unexpected ending, deal with it as it comes,
we're aiming for first place
i can feel it donna toki datte hikari o shinjiteru
I Can Feel it, no matter what, I believe in the light
nigirishime ta yume ga koboreochi sou na
When the dream I've attained is
toki ni kagitte omoidasu no
about to fall apart, I remember
aitsu no ano yasashii kao
His kind expression,
mune no oku ga mata tsuyoku nareru no
the core of my heart is strengthened once again
bukkirabou no kokoro ni fire
My blunt mind is set ablaze,
gutto kuru ashita o tsukami tain da
I want to grasp tomorrow as it comes at me
mada mi nu sekai wa kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of the world I haven't seen,
shinji ta mirai desho hora let’s try!
isn't this the future we believed in? Come on Let's try!
kazoekire nai ano namida wa sou sa niji ni kawaru darou
Those countless tears, will they change into a rainbow?
osaekire nai kanashimi mo
That sorrow I can't contain
itsuka wa dakishime rareru ka na
Will I be able to embrace you someday?
yawa na haato ga uzukidashi tara
When my feeble heart begins to throb
arittake asu ni kisu shite ageyou
I give all of my kisses to tomorrow
furue ta mama no chiisana kobushi o tsuyoku mata nigitte
Still trembling, I clench my tiny fist tightly
dondengaeshi detatokoshoubu nerau wa ittou shou
An unexpected ending, deal with it as it comes,
we're aiming for first place
i can feel it donna toki datte hikari o shinjiteru
I Can Feel it, no matter what, I believe in the light
The Cursed Puppet
(いの)ねえ 巻物は揃ってるし➡
Hey, we have both scrolls,
so let's go straight for the goal.
一直線に ゴールしちゃおうよ。
(チョウジ)そうしたいけどね。
I wish we could,
待ち伏せを受ける
可能性が高いと➡
but there's a high risk of
getting ambushed.
やっぱりサクラの作戦どおり
迂回ルートで…。
We should stick to Sakura's plan
and take the detour.
(チョウジ)サクラ？
(いの)ん？
Sakura...?
(いの)あっ サクラ!?
Sakura!
(サクラ)ハァ ハァ ハァ。
サクラ。
Sakura...
ハァ ハァ…。
２つの… ダム。
Two dams...
((綱手 : これから教えるのは➡
Next, I'm going to teach you
the jutsu to revive all the organs,
すべての器官 組織を再生する術。
the entire system.
その名も忍法 創造再生。
It's called the Ninja Art:
Mitotic Regeneration Jutsu.
忍法 創造再生？
Ninja Art...
Mitotic Regeneration?
これは回復能力の術ではない。
This isn't a jutsu that revolves
around healing skills.
初代火影が使っていたのと同じ➡
It's the same kind of
regeneration jutsu
再生能力の術だ。
that the First Hokage used.
(綱手)初代は膨大なチャクラを
持っていたため➡
The First Hokage had
such enormous chakra that
印を結ぶことなく発動していた。
he could activate it
without weaving signs.
そんな大量のチャクラ
私にはありません。
I don't have
that kind of immense chakra.
そこで もう１つ教える術がある。
So... there's one more jutsu
I will teach you.
百豪の術だ。
It's called
The 100 Healings Jutsu.
百豪の術？
The 100 Healings Jutsu?
私にも初代ほどのチャクラはない。
Even I don't have the kind of chakra
that the First Hokage had.
そこで開発したのが この術だ。
So I developed this jutsu.
この術を使えば➡
By using it, you can keep
a huge amount of chakra in reserve.
大量のチャクラを
ためておくことができる。
(綱手)この２つを
併用することにより➡
By combining these two,
体は再生し続け
その間 死ぬことはなくなる。
the body will continue
to regenerate and
you will not die during that time.
(サクラ)す すごい。
A-Amazing...
(綱手)しかしな➡
問題なのは百豪の術だ。
However, there's a problem with
The 100 Healings Jutsu.
至極緻密なチャクラコントロールを
必要とするうえ➡
Not only does it require extremely
delicate chakra control,
３年間 一定のチャクラを➡
you must amass chakra
for three years.
ため続けなければならない。
(サクラ)３年も…。
Three years...?
(綱手)うむ 一定のチャクラが
練られているな。
You have a constant amount
of chakra infused.
その状態を３年間
維持するんだぞ。
Well, you must maintain
that state for three years!
くっ…。
100 HEALINGS
《この状態で３年間も…》
I have to maintain this condition
for three years?!
はぁ～！
あぁ…。
(綱手)サクラ！
Sakura!
ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
百豪の影響で ふだん使える➡
Due to the effect of
The 100 Healings Jutsu,
チャクラの量が
極端に少なくなっている。
your normal chakra level
has become extremely low.
これでは
治療や戦闘に支障をきたす。
This will only be a hindrance
during healing and in battle.
手術も前に出て戦うことも➡
At this rate, I can't allow you
to perform any surgery
許可することはできんぞ。
or go out into the battlefield.
百豪の術とは別に➡
The 100 Healings Jutsu creates
a smaller secondary dam
チャクラをためておくことができる➡
in which to store
the chakra reserve...
小さなダムを もう１つ作る。
２つのダムのチャクラを➡
If I keep two dams of chakra and
目的別に使い分ければ➡
make sure I use each of them
for their specific purpose...
手術も前に出て戦うことも➡
I should be able to perform surgery
as well as fight in battles!
(可能になるはず))
あっ！
いの チョウジ！ 敵？
Ino! Choji!
Is it an enemy?
(サクラ)人形!?
A doll?
(サヤ)ウフフフッ ほんとにいい子ですわ。
You're such a good girl...
(サヤ)獲物を見つけてくれるなんて。
... for finding me some prey.
サクラ 体のほうは大丈夫？
Sakura, are you holding up physically?
うん 休ませてもらったから。
Yes, since you let me rest...
(サナ)お姉様 さっさと
殺しちゃいましょうよ。
Elder Sister,
let's hurry and kill them.
(マムシ)そんなに焦んなよ。
サヤお嬢が怒るぜ。
Don't be so hasty, Sana.
You'll get Saya mad.
お姉様だって➡
I'm sure Elder Sister wants to
get this over with quickly too.
とっとと片づけたいに
決まってるじゃない。
(サナ)ねぇ お姉様。
Right, Elder Sister...?
ヘヘヘヘッ！ ならば… うおっ。
All right then...
サヤ てめえ！ ひいっ。
Saya, damn you...!
サヤ… お嬢様。
L-Lady Saya!
私のお人形が見つけた獲物➡
I shall take my time...
じっくり呪ってさしあげる
ことにしますわ。
and curse these victims
that my doll has found.
じゃ じゃあ
どいつからやるんだよ！
Th-Then which one
will we kill first?
ですか…。
そうね➡
Let's see...
ウフフフッ ２人とも
とってもかわいいのですわ。
They are both quite cute...
やりがいがありそう。
う～ん デブはいらない。
They will be worth killing.
I don't want the fatso...
デブ！ てめえは俺の獲物だ！
Fatso!
You're mine!
僕は… ぽっちゃり系だ！
I... am...
pleasingly plump!
言い方 変えても デブはデブだ！
Put it any way you like.
A fatso's still a fatso!
グヘヘヘッ！
こいつ… やばい。
チョウジ！
This guy's dangerous!
Choji!
じゃあ 私は金髪を。
あの子は私の。
Then I'll take the blonde one.
She is mine.
じゃあ おでこを。
あれも私の。
Then one with
the big forehead...
She is mine as well.
デブ！
Fatso!
(チョウジ)ぽっちゃり系だって～の！
I said I'm pleasingly plump!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
部分倍化の術！
グヘヘッ 危なかったぜ。
That was close!
チョウジ！
Choji!
あいつ… 傀儡使い！
She's... a Puppet User!
あなたは呪われた。
You have been cursed.
もう この子から逃げられない。
You can no longer...
escape from her.
《相手が傀儡使いなら
術者さえやれば…》
If she's the Puppet User,
as long as we bring down
the jutsu caster...
サクラ 私の体を。
Sakura, my body...!
任せて。
Leave it to me!
Mind...!
心転身の…。
傀儡もどきの術。
Puppet Imitation Jutsu.
いの？
Ino...?
いの!?
Ino?!
(チョウジ)うわぁ！
チョウジ！
Choji!
《私がやるしかない… でも》
It's up to me to do this...
But...
いの！ サクラ！
Ino! Sakura!
仲間を心配してる場合じゃねえぞ。
This is not the time to worry
about your friends.
あなたも大ピンチなのよ。 フフフフッ。
You're in quite a bind too, you know.
超倍化の術！
Super Expansion Jutsu!
食べちゃうぞ～。
I'll eat you!
いの！
Ino!
な 何なの？
W-What is it?
傀儡もどきの術。
Puppet Imitation Jutsu!
術にかけられて わかったわ。
I realized it after I was
under that jutsu.
呪いとかいうのは
傀儡の術なんかじゃない。
She calls it a curse,
but it's not a Puppet Jutsu.
心転身の術に近いものよ。
It's closer to
a Mind Transfer Jutsu.
ああ～！
山中一族の面目丸つぶれ！
Aw man!
The Yamanaka Clan's reputation
is ruined!
(サナ)お姉様 助かりましたわ！
Elder Sister, thanks for
coming to my rescue!
(マムシ)サヤお嬢 あいつらを
叩きのめしてくれ！
Lady Saya!
Curse those guys!
言われるまでもない。
容赦しませんわ。
– There's no need to tell me that.
– I shall show no mercy.
この人形は 私のもの。
This doll is mine...
さぁ おいき！
Now, go!
生意気なお友達に
お仕置きをしておあげ！
Punish your arrogant friends!
(サクラ)い… いの こっち来るわよ。
I-Ino, he's coming this way!
(いの)こうなったら
やっぱり 術者を…。
Then there's only one way.
We have to get the jutsu caster...
いの？
Ino...?
山中一族が 心転身で
負けるわけにはいかないのよ！
No one beats the Yamanaka Clan
in Mind Transfer!
心転身の術！
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
(いの)チョウジ！
あら？
Choji!
Oh?
ダメじゃない
私のお人形さんの中に➡
That's not nice.
You can't enter my doll
without permission...
勝手に入ってきちゃ。
出てって。
Get out!
チョウジは 私たちの仲間よ！
Choji is our friend!
あんたこそ出てって！
フン…。
So you get out!
((これでは 手術も
前に出て戦うことも➡
At this rate, I can't allow you
to perform any surgery
or go out into the battlefront.
(許可することはできんぞ！))
くっ…。
《サクラ : まだだ… まだ チャクラが…》
I need much... much more chakra...
I need much... more chakra...
《あの頃の私は ただ
いつも２人に守られて➡
Back then, I was...
always being protected by those two...
その後ろ姿を見ていただけ。
and watching from behind.
でも もう あの時とは違う。
But times have changed.
If I have chakra, I can fight.
チャクラさえあれば 戦える！》
(大蛇丸)見事なものね。
Isn't that magnificent?
I guess you're just about ready.
順調に仕上がっている
ということかしら。
(サスケ)まだだ。
イタチを倒すには もっと力がいる。
Not yet.
I need more power in order
to take down Itachi.
(カブト)大蛇丸様。
Lord Orochimaru!
先ほど 例の試薬が完成しました。
The aforementioned reagent
has just been completed.
Oh...
(大蛇丸)そう 水月に使うやつね？
The one to test on Suigetsu?
Who is overseeing the experiment?
実験担当は？
(カブト)香燐にやらせます。
I'll have Karin do it.
２人は 今 東アジトだったかしら？
Aren't they both in
the east hideout?
Yes, I'm dispatching
a subordinate right away to bring them.
ええ すぐに部下に運ばせます。
俺が運んでやる。
I'll go get them.
Oh?
あら どういう風の吹き回し？
What brought this on?
フン… ただの暇つぶしだ。
I'm bored, that's all.
(香燐)珍しいこともあるもんだな。
お前が来るなんて。
Wonders never cease.
I can't believe you're here.
気にするな。
Don't worry.
I'm leaving the minute
I'm done here.
用が済んだら すぐ帰る。
I-I'm not worried!
べべ 別に気にしてないし！
Anyway, you're late bringing
the medicine!
ってか
クスリ 届くの遅すぎだろ。
(水月)あ～あ キミが大蛇丸の
パシリだなんてがっかりだよ。
I'm so disappointed that
Orochimaru's lackey is you.
I sure hope you don't plan
(水月)まさか こいつみたいに➡
on becoming Orochimaru's pet
like this one.
大蛇丸の ペットに
なり下がる気じゃないだろうね。
Who did you call a pet?!
誰がペットだ こら！
I'm going to get ready
for the experiment.
うちは 実験の準備にかかる。
サスケ お前もこんなやつ
相手にするな。
Sasuke, don't bother with this guy!
Sasuke, seriously...
Will you help me?
(水月)サスケ マジで助けてくんない？
I'm sick and tired of this place.
こんな場所 もううんざりだ。
それは お前の力次第だ。
That all depends on your strength.
Sheesh...
(水月)チェッ。
Hey...
おい。
えっ。
あ…。
Aw man, what kind of horrible experiment
is it gonna be this time?
やれやれ どんなえぐい実験が
始まるのやら…。
あ～。
Hey, you...!
おい お前！
You fool, what are you doing?!
バカ！ 何やってんだ！
ラッキー！
Lucky me!
You let Suigetsu escape...?!
(香燐)水月を逃がしただと!?
When I came to,
everything was like this.
自分が気がついたときには
このありさまで…。
Damn it!
クソ！ こんなことがバレたら➡
If Lord Orochimaru finds out
about this, he'll take it out on me!
大蛇丸様に
むちゃくちゃ怒られる！
We're going after him now!
Round up everyone!
すぐに追うぞ！
みんなを集めてこい！
はっ！
それで何とかなる相手なのか？
And what good will
that do against him?
サスケ お前 まだいたのか？
Sasuke! You're still here?!
実験を見ていくのも
悪くないかと思ってな。
I figured it might be interesting
to watch the experiment.
Anyway, what will you do?
それより どうする？
どうするって…。
Do...?
Since I'm here,
I'll lend you a hand.
ついでだ
お前に手を貸してやる。
あっちだ！
Over that way...
１時の方向！
感知能力か。
Towards 1 o'clock!
Sensory Perception?
ああ 知ってる相手なら
離れていてもチャクラを追える。
Yeah, if it's someone I know,
I can go after their chakra.
That's convenient.
便利だな だが腑に落ちない。
But I don't get it.
With that kind of power,
それほどの力があれば➡
I'd think you could get away
from Orochimaru.
大蛇丸から
逃げられそうなものだが。
なぜって…。
That's because...
((あぁ～！ 助けて！
Help!
I'll bet this redhead
is a remnant
この赤い髪 うずしおの生き残りに
間違いなさそうだ。
of a clan from the Hidden Eddies...
You were right that
she'd be worth something.
小遣い稼ぎに寄って
正解だったな。
Let me go! Let me go!
離して！ 離してよ！
She's a pretty feisty kid.
往生際の悪いガキだぜ。
I hear you have an unusual power.
お前ら 珍しい力を
持ってるんだってな。
We'll get a good price
for you underground.
そういう忍は
地下で高く売れるんだよ。
ヘヘヘ…。
A shinobi without a homeland
(大蛇丸)故郷をなくした
忍っていうのは➡
is quite tragic.
哀れなものね。 どこかの里に
身をよせたところで➡
No matter where you end up,
you're treated like a outcast.
しょせん 異端者扱い。
And if you possess attributes
that are unusual,
おまけに 特殊体質ともなれば
どこへ行っても狙われる。
they come after you...
as long as you're living.
生きてる限りずっと。
Well... I speak as
one of the hunted too.
まあ そういう私も
狙う側なんだけど フフフ…。
でもね
どうせなら自分で決めなさい。
But, you know...
You must decide for yourself.
If you come with me,
no one will ever touch you again.
(私のもとに来れば もう誰も
あなたに手は出せないわ))
どうせ従うなら
力のあるやつがいい。
If I have to follow someone...
I'd rather it be someone strong.
So if I'm stronger than Orochimaru,
you'd follow me?
つまり 大蛇丸より
俺が強ければ➡
乗りかえる気はあるってことか。
Damn, a river...
(香燐)チッ！ 川か やっかいだな。
What a nuisance.
気をつけろよ サスケ。
Watch out, Sasuke.
We may not see him, but he's here.
姿はないが やつはここにいる。
Yeah.
ああ。
I guess I can't fool you.
やっぱり 騙し討ちには
やられないか。
But...
でも キミまで
追いかけて来るとはね。
I didn't expect you
to be with her.
Sasuke follows Lord Orochimaru!
サスケは 大蛇丸様のもとにいるんだ。
What did you expect?!
当然だろ。
キミは黙ってよ。
You be quiet.
Hey, Sasuke...
ねえ サスケ どうせなら➡
If you're willing to follow her,
why not come with me instead?
あの女じゃなくて 僕につかない？
Huh?! What're you saying, idiot?!
はあ!? 何言ってんだよ お前！
I have no reason to argue with you.
キミとやり合う理由はないんだしさ。
Don't ignore me!
無視すんな！
I already answered that question.
その答えなら もう伝えたはずだ。
Oh yeah... you did say it
all depends on my strength?
そういえば 僕の力次第って
言ってたっけ？
A Water Clone!
水分身！
Physical attacks don't work on him!
そいつに
物理攻撃は効かない！ 雷遁を！
Use Lightning Style...!
I won't let you weave any signs...
印なんか結ばせないよっ！
(香燐)サスケ！
Sasuke!
I'm so sorry, Sasuke...
ごめんね サスケ君。
Just kidding!
なんちゃって。
へえ～ いい刀だね。
Hey, that's a nice blade.
Well then...
さ～て 次はキミの番だよ。
You're next...
おとなしく一緒に戻れ。
Just obey and return with me.
Or you'll regret it.
じゃないと 後悔することになる。
What? Is that a threat?
何それ。 脅しのつもり？
なんだよ 今の…。
What was that just now?
As expected...
It even worked on you.
さすがに お前にも効いただろ…。
Lord Orochimaru said...
《この鎖は
チャクラの塊だって縛れるって➡
that this chain can even bind
a mass of chakra.
大蛇丸様は言ってたけど…。
But I had never used it before.
まだ 自在に使うとこまでは…》
That's enough, Karin.
もういい。 香燐 それをしまえ。
Put that away.
Huh? Sasuke...
あれ？ サスケ…。
しまうんだ。
Put it away.
In time, I'll get these two
on my side.
《この２人
いずれは俺の仲間にする。
それだけの力を持っている》
Their powers will be worth it.
Ino's Mind Transfer failed?
《いのの心転身が負けた!?》
Not yet... I don't have
enough chakra yet...
《まだ… チャクラが！》
hitori ja nai yo
You're not alone
osoreru mono nante nai kara
There's nothing to be afraid of
ikou saa me o ake te
Let's go, now open your eyes
butsukatte ita
I was crashing into you
hontou wa oitsuki taku te
I just wanted to catch up so badly
kizutsuke atte
We hurt one another
tsunagi tomeru kizuna hoshiku te
I just wanted a bond to connect me to you
"gomen" wasure nai de
"I'm sorry" Don't forget
shinji te matte te
Trust in me and wait
mukae ni ikun da
I'll come for you
yuuki no tomoshibi terashidase yowa sa o
The light of courage, reveal our weaknesses
kizu datte itami datte wakeae ba heiki da
If we share our wounds and pain, we'll be fine
kimi no senaka osu musun da yakusoku
This is the promise I made you push you forward
itsu datte hanare tatte
No matter when, even if we're apart
shinjirareru kizuna wa mune ni nemutteru
The bond I believe in rests in my heart
Choji and Ino are using up
their chakra
due to all these successive battles.
Their strength and willpower
are at their limits!
Back then, all I ever did
皆さん こんばんは。
前川清です。
was have Sasuke and Naruto
protect me.
今 私たちは
東京の有楽町に来ております。
Now, I should be able
to protect them...
Like Naruto and Sasuke
did back then!
夜になりますと
この有楽町 家路に急ぐ方➡
あるいは 一杯飲みに行く方
いらっしゃいますよね。
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Their Backs"
いろんな思いの方が たくさん
いらっしゃるんでしょうね。
I can't be whining about
my weaknesses here!
今回の 「モクハチ」は
有楽町にあります➡
東京国際フォーラムより
２時間スペシャルをお送りいたします。